[
  {"id": 1, "problem": "30+50=", "answer": 80, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 2, "problem": "24+45=", "answer": 69, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 3, "problem": "70-60=", "answer": 10, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 4, "problem": "85-23=", "answer": 62, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 5, "problem": "23+5=", "answer": 28, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 6, "problem": "56+3=", "answer": 59, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 7, "problem": "68-4=", "answer": 64, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 8, "problem": "39-6=", "answer": 33, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 9, "problem": "98-20=", "answer": 78, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 10, "problem": "88-30=", "answer": 58, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 11, "problem": "44+10=", "answer": 54, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 12, "problem": "76+11=", "answer": 87, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 13, "problem": "34+8=", "answer": 42, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 14, "problem": "25+9=", "answer": 34, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 15, "problem": "48+6=", "answer": 54, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 16, "problem": "57+9=", "answer": 66, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 17, "problem": "56+14=", "answer": 70, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 18, "problem": "25+46=", "answer": 71, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 19, "problem": "45+15=", "answer": 60, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 20, "problem": "54+29=", "answer": 83, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 21, "problem": "78-9=", "answer": 69, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 22, "problem": "41-9=", "answer": 32, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 23, "problem": "81-7=", "answer": 74, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 24, "problem": "72-7=", "answer": 65, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 25, "problem": "65-37=", "answer": 28, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 26, "problem": "36-18=", "answer": 18, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 27, "problem": "93-87=", "answer": 6, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 28, "problem": "83-46=", "answer": 37, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 29, "problem": "65-59=", "answer": 6, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 30, "problem": "93-26=", "answer": 67, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 31, "problem": "35+29+18=", "answer": 82, "type": "三个数加法"},
  {"id": 32, "problem": "18+20+33=", "answer": 71, "type": "三个数加法"},
  {"id": 33, "problem": "98-43-27=", "answer": 28, "type": "三个数减法"},
  {"id": 34, "problem": "87-18-25=", "answer": 44, "type": "三个数减法"},
  {"id": 35, "problem": "45+17-24=", "answer": 38, "type": "混合运算"},
  {"id": 36, "problem": "54+28-33=", "answer": 49, "type": "混合运算"},
  {"id": 37, "problem": "76-18+25=", "answer": 83, "type": "混合运算"},
  {"id": 38, "problem": "89-61+14=", "answer": 42, "type": "混合运算"},
  {"id": 39, "problem": "85-47-38=", "answer": 0, "type": "三个数减法"},
  {"id": 40, "problem": "95-32-17=", "answer": 46, "type": "三个数减法"}
]